=== Plugin Name ===

Plugin Name: GMO Ads Master
Author: WP Shop byGMO
Author URI: http://www.wpshop.com
Contributors: WP Shop byGMO
Tags: Slider, Simple, Effects
Requires at least: 3.8.1
Tested up to: 3.9 Beta
Stable tag: Version 1.0 
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html

== Description ==

GMO Ads Master is the ad banner plugin which enables you to place ad contents to the desired locations such as inside article, sidebar and footer.  In addition to that, using this plugin let you setup Google Analytics tracking code and sitemap tool settings, and sitemap can be easily generated without playing with PHP files.

== Instruction  ==

Install plugin and activate.  Open [GMO Ads Master] in Settings. 

Setting up Google Webmaster Tool
1. Attach meta key on Verification in [Stats Settings] option.
2. Verify website with Google Webmaster Tool. 
3. Copy Your Sitemap URL on [Stats Settings], and register sitemap using Google Webmaster Tool. 

Setting up Google Analytics
1. Copy Google Analytics tracking code and paste on the Google Analytics Code in [Stats Settings].

Place ad banner on website
*Up to 3 ads can be placed.
*Location can be set using all widgets.

1. Enter arbitrary title on [Advertising Name] in [Advertising Codes]
2. Attach ad code such as Google Adsense on [Advertising Code]. 
3. Up to 3 ads can be generated. 
4. Open [Appearance], [Widgets] and select [GMO Ads Master] in the Available Widgets, and drag to the position you wish to place. 
5. Select which ad banner to show out of 3, and choose layout from left/center/right. 
6. Save. 

[Share Buttons] section allows you to select icons to use.  Simply drag icons you wish to use into 'Activated Services' area and icons.  




== Installation ==

Search and download plugin from either WordPress admin page or http://wordpress.org/plugins.  From the WordPress admin page, simply activate the plugin, or upload a file from "Add New" to install and activate plug-in.  

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

== Changelog == 

-Initial Release

== Upgrade Notice ==

== Screenshots ==
screenshot-1.png

